Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 4: Committee Files, 1920-2007; (71 Boxes)
  - Subseries 4.1: Topic-Business/Local Committees, 1920-1980; (22 Boxes)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Nominations, 1956 (Box 125, Folder 49)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Resolutions, 1956 (Box 125, Folder 50)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Time and Place, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee (1), 1956 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee (2), 1956 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee (3), 1956 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - NCCC Conference - Final Program, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - NCCC Conference - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - NCCC Conference - Preliminary Program, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - NCCC Conference - Registration, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - NCCC Conference - Reports of Integrated Days, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - NCCC Conference - Suggestions for Program, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Meetings, 1956 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Nominations, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Resolutions, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Time and Place, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - NCCC Conference - Conference Registration, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - NCCC Conference - Publicity, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - NCCC Conference - Homemaker Service - Material Compiled for Workshop, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - NCCC Conference - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - NCCC Conference - Proceedings, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee (1), 1957 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee (2), 1957 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - NCCC Conference - Preliminary Program, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - NCCC Conference - Final Program, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - NCCC Conference - Regional Meeting - Phoenix, Arizona, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Meetings, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 27)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Regional Meeting, 1957 (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - NCCC Conference - Annual Business Session, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - NCCC Conference - Annual Meeting Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Nominations, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 31)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Resolutions, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - NCCC Conference - Publicity, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - NCCC Conference - Registration, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 34)
    - NCCC Conference - News Letter - Program Committee, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - NCCC Conference - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 37)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee on Time and Place, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 38)
    - NCCC Conference - Letter of Thanks, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 39)
    - NCCC Conference - Final Program, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 40)
    - NCCC Conference - Preliminary Program, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 41)
    - NCCC Conference - Proposed Regional Meetings, 1941-1958 (Box 126, Folder 42)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Meetings, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 43)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 44)
    - NCCC Conference - Reports of Workshops, 1958 (Box 126, Folder 45)
    - NCCC Conference - Advance and Final Programs, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 46)
    - NCCC Conference - Annual Business Session, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 47)
    - NCCC Conference - Committees on Nominations, Time and Place, and Resolutions, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 48)
    - NCCC Conference - Finances, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 49)
    - NCCC Conference - Letters of Thanks, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 50)
    - NCCC Conference - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 51)
    - NCCC Conference - Proceedings, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 52)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 53)
    - NCCC Conference - Publicity, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - NCCC Conference - Registration, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - NCCC Conference - Regional Meeting - San Francisco, California, 1958-1959 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Meetings, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Regional Meeting - Charlotte, North Carolina, 1957-1959 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Regional Meeting - Louisville, Kentucky, 1958-1959 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshop Announcement, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshop Reports, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - NCCC Conference - Annual Business Session, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - NCCC Conference - Art Exhibit, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee to Study Planned Parenthood (1), 1947-1961 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee to Study Planned Parenthood (2), 1947-1961 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - NCCC Conference - Committee to Study Translation of Conference Publications, 1959-1961 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - NCCC Conference - Final Program, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - NCCC Conference - Golden Jubilee - Art Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - NCCC Conference - Golden Jubilee of the Conference, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - NCCC Conference - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - NCCC Conference - Proceedings (1), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - NCCC Conference - Proceedings (2), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - NCCC Conference - Program Committee, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - NCCC Conference - Publicity (1), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - NCCC Conference - Publicity (2), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - NCCC Conference - Registration, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Regional Meeting - Miami, Florida, 1959-1960 (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - NCCC Conference - Thank You Letters, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops Announcement and Schedule, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops - Correspondence and Reports (1), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - NCCC Conference - Workshops - Correspondence and Reports (2), 1960 (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Advance Program, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Annual Meeting Buzz Sessions, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 31)
    - Final Program, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 32)
    - Letters of Thanks, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 33)
    - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 34)
    - Program Committee, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 35)
    - Registration, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 36)
    - NCCC Conference - Southeastern Regional Meeting - Richmond, Virginia, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 37)
    - NCCC Conference - Southwestern Regional Meeting - (Planned for Albuquerque, New Mexico - Not Held), 1960-1961 (Box 127, Folder 38)
    - Workshops, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence Regarding Program, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Program Committee, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Southeastern Regional Meeting (1), 1962 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Regional Meeting (2), 1962 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Southeastern Regional Meeting (3), 1962 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Southwestern Regional Meeting, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Workshops, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting-Medical Social Workers, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting-Opinion Questionnaire, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting-SVDP Program, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Comments on Program, 1962-1963 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Committees on Nomination, Time and Place, Resolutions, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Conference of Religious Program, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence re: Proceedings, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Exhibits, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Final Program, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - General and Special Meetings, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Hotel Statler-Cleveland, 1961-1963 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Integrated Days, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Job Information Exchange, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Letters of Thanks, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Local Committee on Arrangements, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Program Committee, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Schools of Social Work, Social Hours, Ladies of Charities Tea, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Southeast Regional Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Southwest Regional Meeting, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Workshops, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Youth Conference, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Commission on the Aging, 1963-1964 (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Commission on the Aging, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 31)
    - Commission on Families and Children (1), 1964 (Box 128, Folder 32)
    - Commission on Families and Children (2), 1964 (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - Committees on Nominatin, Time and Place, and Resolutions, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 34)
    - Committee on Relationship Between NCCC and Catholic International Union, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 35)
    - Conference of Religious Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Estimates of Requirements for Workshop Materials, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 37)
    - Exhibits, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 38)
    - La Salle Hotel, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 39)
    - Local Arrangements-St. Louis, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 40)
    - Meetings for Medical Social Services, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 41)
    - Program Committee, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 42)
    - Program-St. Louis Msgr. Gallagher Correspondence with Speakers, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 43)
    - Regional Meeting-Diocese of Tucson (1), 1964 (Box 128, Folder 44)
    - Regional Meeting-Diocese of Tucson (2), 1964 (Box 128, Folder 45)
    - Workshops, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 46)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Aging, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Commission on Families and Children, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Committees on Nomination, Time and Place, and Resolutions, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Conference of Religious-Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Local Committee on Arrangements-Philadelphia, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Program Committee, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Workshops and Preliminary Program, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Workshop for Major Superiors of Women, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting-Comments, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting-Thank You Letters, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Commission on Families and Children (1), 1966 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Commission on Families and Children (2), 1966 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Commission on Families and Children (3), 1966 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Nominiations, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Time and Place, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Conference of Religious Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Coordinating Committee of Constituent Groups of NCCC, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - NCCC-Institute, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Papers at Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Program-Msgr. Corcoran's File, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Program-Speakers, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 26)
    - Program Committee, 1966 (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Annual Business Session, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting-General, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting-Compliments, Complaints, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Annual Meeting-Institute, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 31)
    - Commission on Aging (1), 1963-1967 (Box 129, Folder 32)
    - Commission on Aging (2), 1963-1967 (Box 129, Folder 33)
    - Commission on Aging-Mailing List, 1964-1967 (Box 129, Folder 34)
    - Commission on the Aging, 1965-1967 (Box 129, Folder 35)
    - Commission on the Aging, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 36)
    - Commission on Families and Children, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 37)
    - Commission on Families and Children, 1967 (Box 129, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Theology, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Time and Place, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Guaranteed Annual Income Material, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Finances, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Program, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Program Committee, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Semi-annual Meeting, St. Louis, April, 1967 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting Program, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Commission on the Aging, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Families and Children, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Committees on Nominations, time and Place, Resolutions, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Finances, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Income Maintenance Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Income Maintenance Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Income Maintenance Committee, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Membership Committee, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Program Committee, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Semi-Annual Meeting of the NCCC, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Annual Business Meeting-Houston, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Aging (1), 1969 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Commission on Aging (2), 1969 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - Commission on Family and Children, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Theology and Catholic Charities, 1967-1969 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Finances, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Membership Committee, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Public Welfare and Income Maintenance Committee, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Semi-annual Meeting, Chicago, April, 1969 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Aging, 1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Day Care, 1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Family and Children, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Directions for Services in the 70s, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Time and Place, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Finance Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Proceedings, 1969-1970 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Proceeding Papers, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Program, 1970 (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Annual Business Session, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting-Bishops' Dinner, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting-Handbook, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting-Rough Draft of McBrien Presentation, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Catholic Charities Appeal, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Commission on Aging, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Committee on Nominations, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 25)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 26)
    - Committee to Study NCCC, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 27)
    - Housing Commission, 1969-1971 (Box 131, Folder 28)
    - Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 29)
    - Program Committee, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 30)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 31)
    - Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 32)
    - Commission on Aging, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Permanent Diaconate, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 34)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 35)
    - Committee on Social Development and World Peace, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 36)
    - Nominating Committee, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 37)
    - Program Committee, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 38)
    - Resolutions Committee, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 39)
    - Commission on Aging, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 40)
    - Commission on Families and Children, 1968-1973 (Box 131, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Credentials Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Advisory Committee, 1966-1973 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Membership Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Nominating Committee Meeting, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Commission on Aging, 1968-1974 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Housing (1), 1969-1974 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Housing (2), 1969-1974 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Services to Unmarried Parents, 1968-1974 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Resolutions, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Committee to Study Mainland China, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Finances, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Membership Committee, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Nominating Committee (1), 1974 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Nominating Committee (2), 1974 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Nominating Committee (3), 1974 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Nominating Committee-Msgr. Corcoran's File, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Aging, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Finance Committee, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Finances, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - Institute on Services to Unmarried Parents, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Membership Committee, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 25)
    - Nominating Committee (1), 1975 (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - Nominating Committee (2), 1975 (Box 132, Folder 27)
    - Nominating Committee (3), 1975 (Box 132, Folder 28)
    - Nominating Committee-Msgr Corcoran's File, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 29)
    - Commission on Aging, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 30)
    - Committee on Day Care, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 31)
    - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice-Social Services, 1966-1976 (Box 132, Folder 32)
    - Credential Committee, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 33)
    - Finance Committee, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 34)
    - Membership Committee, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 35)
    - Nominating Committee (1), 1976 (Box 132, Folder 36)
    - Nominating Committee (2), 1976 (Box 132, Folder 37)
    - Resolutions Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Commission on Aging (1), 1977 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Commission on Aging (2), 1977 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee, 1977 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee (1), 1977 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Nominating Committee (2), 1977 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Program Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Aging (1), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Aging (2), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Nominations (1), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Nominations (2), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Nominating Committee, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Program Committee (1), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Program Committee (2), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Resolutions Committee, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Resources Committee Meeting, November, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Resources Committee (1), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Resources Committee (2), 1978 (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Aging, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - Nominating Committee (1), 1979 (Box 133, Folder 22)
    - Nominating Committee (2), 1979 (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - Program Committee, 1979 (Box 133, Folder 24)
    - Special Committee, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting-Orientation Materials, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting-Registration Program Proof 3, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Annual Meeting-Registration Program, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Annual Meeting-Program Committee, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting-Printing, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting-Schedule, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Annual Meeting-Badges, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Annual Meeting-Final Program Proof 1, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting-Final Program, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting-Expenses, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Annual Meeting-Rochester Bag Stuff, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Annual Meeting-Work Schedule, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Annual Meeting-Photographs, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting-Committee, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - Annual Meeting-Photographs, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 24)
    - Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting Registration Program (1), 2000 (Box 134, Folder 26)
    - Annual Meeting Registration Program (2), 2000 (Box 134, Folder 27)
    - Annual Meeting Anniversary Poster, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 28)
    - Annual Meeting Anniversary Timeline, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 29)
    - Annual Meeting Ninetieth (90th) Anniversary, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 30)
    - Annual Meeting-Final Program, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 31)
    - Annual Meeting-Committee, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 32)
    - Annual Meeting-Newark, New Jersey, 2001 (Box 134, Folder 33)
  - Subseries 4.2: Diocesan Directors of Catholic Charities, 1932-1982; (15 Boxes)
    - Diocesan Directors - Correspondence- Special Letters, 1932 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Diocesan Directors - Memos, 1933 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Diocesan Directors - Confidential Memoranda (1), 1934-1935 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Diocesan Directors - Confidential Memoranda (2), 1934-1935 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Diocesan Directors - Continuing Committee, 1934 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Diocesan Directors Meetings - Memos (1), 1933-1934 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Diocesan Directors Meetings - Memos (2), 1933-1934 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Diocesan Directors - Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee, 1935 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Diocesan Directors - Continuing Committee (1), 1935 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Diocesan Directors - Continuing Committee (2), 1935 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Diocesan Directors - Continuing Committee (3), 1935 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Diocesan Directors - Memos, 1935 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Diocesan Directors - Directors of Catholic Charities Statement - Annual Meeting - Peoria, Illinois, 1935 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Diocesan Directors - Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee (1), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Diocesan Directors - Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee (2), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Diocesan Directors - Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee (3), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Diocesan Directors - Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee (4), 1936 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Diocesan Directors - Continuing Committee, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Diocesan Directors - Memos, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Diocesan Directors - Minutes, 1936 (Box 135, Folder 20)
    - Diocesan Directors -Committee on Policies and Resolutions - Continuing Committee, 1937 (Box 135, Folder 21)